joomclub.org 2013-05-23

# Privacy Policy

JoomClub is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our privacy practices for our website, www.joomclub.org on the World Wide Web (the "Site"), as well as for JoomClub services that may be accessed through the normal use of our products (the "Services"). You can travel through most of our Site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request. The following statement explains our information-gathering and dissemination practices. Please read the complete JoomClub Privacy Policy.

  * General Information
  * Information Collection and Use
  * If You Opt to Receive Communications, How We Will Contact You
  * Site Functionality
  * Security of Your Information
  * Correcting/Updating Personal Information

### General Information

JoomClub may periodically update this Privacy Policy. If so, JoomClub will post the updated Privacy Policy on this Site. JoomClub encourages you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time for any changes.

By using this Site or any products or services provided through the Site, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OF THE TERMS BELOW, YOU SHOULD NOT USE THIS SITE OR THE PRODUCTS OR SERVICES OFFERED BY JoomClub AT THIS SITE.

Please note that the JoomClub Users Forum (coming soon) is covered by its own privacy policy, which is available for review at any time.

### Information Collection and Use

You may decide whether to proceed with any activity that requests personally identifiable information. If you do not wish to provide the requested information, however, you may not be able to complete the transaction. We do not collect information from individuals under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, we ask that you do not submit any personal information through the Site. If we have specific knowledge that an individual under the age of 13 has submitted personally identifiable information to the Site, we will delete such information permanently and without notice.

Except as described below, JoomClub will only disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties if acting under a good faith belief that such action is necessary (1) to conform to legal requirements; (2) to protect and defend the rights or property of JoomClub ; (3) to enforce the JoomClub Terms of Service; or (4) in the event of a merger, acquisition or sale of all or substantially all JoomClub' assets relating to the business in connection with which the information was collected. JoomClub collects personally identifiable information that can be divided into the following categories:

**JoomClub Product Registration Information:** Some JoomClub products ask you for certain personally identifiable information as part of the installation/registration process (including but not limited to your name, email address, credit card information and connection type and number of computers). Certain of this information is necessary in order to conclude the transaction, and for applicable products, to be eligible to receive technical support. If you provide us with personally identifiable information, and select the "Inform me about important updates and news" option on the purchase confirmation page or in the in the "Registration Information" section located in the "Configuration Panel" of the "Control Panel" in the JoomClub product, we use this information to send you communications, including informative emails/newsletters about JoomClub product upgrades, product updates, new products, and services, and to provide you with special offers that may be of interest to you, including paid advertisements from third parties. In the event you no longer wish to receive such information, you may choose to opt out of receiving further communications by complying with the procedures listed in the "Updating/Unsubscribing Your Email Address" section of this Privacy Policy. Except in the case of Partner Products (see below), JoomClub keeps personally identifiable information collected in the course of installation/registration of JoomClub' products confidential and does not sell, trade, or exchange mailing lists with any organization.

**Credit Card Information** : If you use a credit card to purchase products via this Site, your name as it appears on the credit card, the credit card number, expiration date and billing address will be encrypted as it passes over the Internet. JoomClub does not record or keep your credit card information for online credit-card transactions; rather such information is simply passed through to our contracted payment processing vendor. JoomClub may access such information through the payment processing company, but does not do so except to process refunds or adjustments and to the extent necessary in the event of nonpayment or disputed payments, or as may be necessary for JoomClub' compliance, in JoomClub' discretion, with applicable law.

**Technical Support** : If you request technical support online, we will ask you for information necessary to complete the transaction such as your name, email address and information about your computer hardware, software, and the nature of the problem you are experiencing. In the course of providing support, your data may be transmitted to service providers that are under contract to JoomClub and have agreed to abide by the provisions of this privacy policy. Such transmissions of your data are encrypted and secure.

**Partner Application** : If you request participation in the partner program online, we will ask you for information necessary to complete the transaction such as company name, email address, and company profile.

### If You Opt to Receive Communications, How We Will Contact You

**Email** : With your permission, JoomClub will send you communications, including informative emails/newsletters about product upgrades, product updates, new products, and services. These communications provide you with special offers that may be of interest to you. JoomClub uses a third-party program of outbound email technology to send email from our servers and does not collect information about you but does collect requests to unsubscribe.

### Site Functionality

**Cookies** : A "cookie" is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our Site. Once you close your browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our Site, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our Site. You may still use our Site if you reject the cookie. The only drawback to this is that you will be limited in some areas of our Site. For example, you will not be able to use certain features of our forum or other parts of the Site that offer customized settings.

**Log Files** : We (JoomClub and/or our contracted web analytics provider(s)) do keep track of the domains from which you access our Site and Services on the World Wide Web, and may log IP addresses or other identifiers for statistical purposes. We do this to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use to identify and analyze trends and the results ofour marketing efforts, to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Site and Services, and analyze users' movements. We may periodically share aggregate demographic information with our business partners. IP addresses and other identifiers are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links** : This Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we JoomClub are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Site.

**Newsletter** : If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.

### Security of Your Information

All information gathered on the Site is stored and maintained in secure facilities. In addition, internal security provides that this information is coded with restricted access, and our servers are kept in a secure, locked environment that limits access to authorized personnel only. All JoomClub employees, and all external service providers who may process and/or store customer data, are briefed about the company's privacy and security policies on a regular basis. The Site is regularly tested for security breaches to ensure that all information collected is secure from unauthorized viewing. Any service providers with whom JoomClub contracts, and who receive, store, or process personally identifiable customer data, have committed to abide by the provisions of this privacy policy. All transmissions of personally identifiable customer data are encrypted and secure.

If you have any questions about the security at our Site, you can send an email to [info@joomclub.org](mailto:info@joomclub.org).

Please note that this email address will reject messages with attachments of any kind.

### Correcting/Updating Personal Information

You are free to update your information at any time directly through our Site. At your request, JoomClub will change your information; we may request evidence of your identity before doing so. Inasmuch as your information will never be used without your explicit consent, we are not able to update the email address to which you subscribe to JoomClub communications on your behalf. Should you wish to update the email address at which you receive communications from us, please see the next section ("Updating/Unsubscribing Your Email Address") below.

To change your information, or request that your information be changed, please use one of the following options:

  * Log in at http://www.JoomClub.org and click on "Contact Us" link
  * Send email to us at [info@joomclub.org](mailto:info@joomclub.org). Please note that this email address will reject messages with attachments of any kind.
